Hello everyone, this is Mono.
I'm the author of this paper and I'm going to explain about the project and about the
research paper about how it's working.
So let's go.
So this is an introduction and first of all before introduction I just want to narrate
the topic.
This is a topic advanced at the action using machine learning technique with SSH honeypot
and honeypot and integrate approach.
So let's come to the introduction.
So basically we know like we have many service created SSH services.
So coming to the SSH topic first we need to know what is SSH SSH is something like secure
cell server is allows to computers to remotely connect with each other so we can remotely connect
to another system with help of his IP address as well as as password.
So this is a like introducing part so you can read over it.
And so this says about the impact of SSH service in the cybersecurity world about the
RICS.
So my project I'm going to combine the so combined SSH honeypot with muscle learning techniques.
So that's the basic idea of my project and coming to the search problem statement.
So basically the earlier traditional methods they have like they don't have I have
muscle learning techniques they have one in lock pace analysis and they post some experimental
abilities to combat from this issue.
So we are going to integrate the SSH honeypot with muscle learning.
So these are the algorithm I'm you going to use not the algorithm but like these are the
classifiers are there.
Random for us SVM, new ways, decision tree and exhibit and light gpm.
So what base upon the Coyote honeypot data I'm going to use a Coyote honeypot data as
a data set and for our base upon the data set I will use a muscle learning algorithm
on it.
And this is a service survey I have like a there from the sources.
Which is similar to my topic.
So.
And out of 15 other I'm going to explain the 3rd first 3.
So first one is the Jank in at L. So he proposed honeypot identification with multi
fingerprinting.
I mean this exists in system.
So in this I have I found a gap like they don't don't they don't have a classification.
I mean they are basically limited to classification.
I mean they they are completely based upon statistical approach and they don't have very
behavioral patterns.
I mean they can't detect any.
Patterns of the attackers.
So the main idea for honeypot is like a honeypot it will it will it will like mimic the
S is a server.
I mean it will act like a actual server but actually it's not is like a stool to get inside
about that attack us about is motive about is intent and this is the basic kind of a
scope of idea for honeypot.
I already explained what is actually put so this is a data server review.
So the key funding was multi fingerprinting.
The idea of multipriger printing was key funding the first layer changes survey.
So which gradually include I have like improved the detection accuracy.
So coming to the second one.
So second one the firm Mia Filpsia as Jihara so they are working on the third tradition
I mean it's same as my project but still they don't have the lack some automation features
automation extraction capability and also they are also they are only using random forest
as a set to year one.
So in my project I'm using six classifier and talking about the third one and they developed
a muscle running base for water and effects and look but it comes on this as such.
So I did cover this topic.
So limitation about this about this surveys like about the support is that like they don't
have a temporal sequence and as is of attack provision.
I mean same like in the first one they have a bear I mean the first one they have a limitation
about the behavioral pattern and in this they have a limitation of temporal analysis of
attack and what I'm talking about key finding and they used up I mean what a key finding
is they like they literally outperform the traditional signature base and it takes us
systems.
That's a key fighting.
And explain about the three returns of the reviews and let's go to the research gap.
So research gap the overview of existing works.
So I'm going to explain about the existing work works already present in the assesses and
you both will also learn.
So it's existing started.
It's honey pots.
Most of them like primarily rely on the future.
It's a protection.
So what happens if you rely on the future protection.
I mean you can't detect the new and evolving patterns right.
So this is an existing one.
I mean they cannot a dynamic data analysis activities and it of first of all in the distance
away all these papers all this experimental papers they have only used some like two or
three I'll go to like to only use two or three classifiers not more than that.
So that's a limitation.
There's a like research gap is there.
So in my finding I'm going to use six algorithms like this are the six of this.
I'm going to make.
And earlier resource purpose in early scientific paper they have only used one or three
like for us as or as we have that's it.
And go beyond that.
So in my code it doesn't mean that so I'm going to explain all six.
I'm going to indicate all six.
Classify food and food and food and food.
But.
And it's a motivation.
So we know the motivation we're talking about the motivation.
We know how the how the S is a place of white a low in the as I basically stand as
ugly in enterprise level production.
I mean we do the common uses everyone uses I mean everyone bought a transfer of some files.
I want to process up the computing or something fear so basically I've got up trying to
say is like the SS pace of rule.
I mean there's no protection about that.
There's no.
What do you say I mean there's no protection or there's no prevention to find about attackers.
So to eliminate the vulnerability I mean to enhance the security so I plan was there's
already a system about a detection.
So there's no system what a muscle learning part.
I mean if if also the muscle learning part is there but didn't cover the broad console
of muscle learning.
So in my significance I'm going to so I'm going to integrate more algorithm so that there
won't be need of another using another algorithms.
So I covered all algorithms are there.
This is the random forest SVM XZ boost L I GPM and base.
Let's talk about those photos.
This is architecture diagram.
You can see I'm using calculate as it so after they go to see.
All the data will be removed.
All the quiet features are selected.
It will label on the base upon a feature X sector features it will label into two types.
After the labeling into two types again it will go for data training and and and splitting
and based upon the required data and you heard all these algorithm videos.
These are the six or five values and these are the results of this.
The algorithm is not making it easy to decide.
Based upon this muscle learning we will get these three data and let's talk about the
methodology.
Yeah this is a sample calculate as a catalytic asset.
This is how it looks like.
This is a session ID IP address time.
I mean it will connect you have so many features.
So we are based upon the features we are going to predict some analysis as well predict
planning activities.
So in the catalytic asset already already so new.
This is a catalytic asset in this dataset we got like they total 4192 samples are there.
So out of 4192 samples we got my list of samples of 721 and I've been in samples of
3 votes.
And this is a table we have deployed or plotted in table 4 and 5.
It shows that matches models.
I already discussed before.
There we can see this is what I was talking about.
And next this is a accuracy we got in the number 4 is we got 94 support vector 95.
So this all accuracy I got.
I've just plotted all the models accuracy.
This all the all this models.
Exhibus has a high accuracy of 95.83.
So the model is actually predicting this over 15 and under 15 is going on.
See we can say that based upon the results and in last read R.O.C curve is plotted
for the model for coming well.
The prediction is working.
So I have used 6 algorithms.
This algorithm I have used and I have created I was able to obtain a high detection accuracy
in my project of about 95.83% and talking about a feature is a search address.
So we can deploy this in a I mean it's only limited to SS one only only one protocol.
I mean we can we can show some variability in this to in FTP 10.
Let an RTP environment.
I mean we can improve some model performance and show some low latency and real time
data detection.
If we want some data detection.
If we want some variable data or huge study about the tackles we can deploy this project
on it was easy to instance.
Where if you deploy that project on it was easy to instant by doing that we can also find
the geodequist and this I mean these are these 4 other future.
This is a future what what from this.
We can like see our project of our goal of this project is done here was we were successfully
able to integrate SSS and port with machine learning.
And these are the references and talking about the references I have mentioned 16 references
15 references one of the one is the reference to the data set and the here you can see
the website I mean without using data set I have used for this project.
Thank you.